{
    "id": "b64ebf5181044f368419e6c0d0f2fb36",
    "title": "Determiners Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "……………………….. students attended the class.",
            "description": "We use all before a noun without a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The child ate the …………………………. loaf.",
            "description": "The determiner (the) goes before whole whereas it goes after all.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "whole",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Does she have …………………………. wealth?",
            "description": "We use much before an uncountable noun.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… strength he had proved useless.",
            "description": "The little refers to a small amount but it means the whole of that however small it may be.",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "We received …………………………. help from the neighbors.",
            "description": "Little means hardly any.",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "the little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "She has written …………………………… poems.",
            "description": "Many is used with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "much",
                "many",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I have read …………………………. word written by her.",
            "description": "Every is used with singular nouns all is used with plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "every",
                "all",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………… friends he has are all helpful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He is a man of …………………………… words.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… words spoken in earnest will convince him.",
            "description": "A few means 'a small number'",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "The few",
                "A few"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… man must do his duty.",
            "description": "Use every with a singular noun.",
            "answers": [
                "Every",
                "All",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. students attended the class.",
            "description": "Use few with plural nouns and little with uncountable nouns. ",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "Little",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}